[Music]
the working environment in Prudential it
all comes down to the people and the
culture the accessibility to the people
at every level is just incredible it
allows people to connect to bring
themselves on board without really
focusing a lot on the titles but what
people can actually contribute to this
organization that is what makes this
organization really do I really enjoy
working in Prudential where the culture
is very people-oriented my colleagues
are all very friendly and helpful
there were spend time to give me
guidance they I really need other than
work I'm involved in social activities
organized by Prudential a sport and
recreational club in Prudential allows
me to kaname people from various
department in the same company I first
met credential at the Malaysian Career
Fair in London in 2016 and I was like
there for the professional associate
program would interest you look in TRX
next year in preparation for this move
we have a team of unity champions
responsible for keeping all other
employees updated and excited with
regard to the move this team consists of
members from across drop levels and
departments even though I happen to be a
junior staff member I am the unity
champion see what I am trying to say
here is that Prudential recognizes
talents and will go the extra mile to
nurture them
[Music]
to create even a better work environment
and a more dynamic one specifically we
are actually looking into this agile
work place now the goal of this agile
workplace is to break down barriers and
boundaries so that you can actually
promote are more open and a
collaborative work environment and the
whole purpose of actually doing this it
comes down to this a few areas number
one we want to promote with the teamwork
we want to have a greater transparency
at work we want to encourage creativity
but most importantly we want to bring
the team closer together as a team this
is what predation really believes in
that is to make sure that we can always
work together collaborate better to take
us to the next level I also enjoy
volunteering in our company's CSR
activities during my free time progress
that I wanna do including financial
education for children offering free
production plan for Arbor communities
and also providing assistance for
natural disaster relief Prudential
offers a really unique value proposition
for our graduates we have our management
associate program and our professional
associate program which typically spends
between 12 to actually 18 months and
people who actually hire out to this
program gets a lot of leadership
visibility gets to work on life is
projects as well as opportunity to
actually be on an international
assignment in another country
[Music]
so for the greater start there see you
at the Malaysian Career Fair in London
you